I'm keeping one small secret underneath my tiny hat.
I'm a moon-blessed fairy tale werewolf,
and I'm magical at that.
Behind a chilly's where the enchanted free-
Hey, guys.
I had to call this emergency live.
Guys, watch out.
I'm going to calm down a little bit.
I just woke up from my sleep.
And you know, Christine, that horrible witch.
She's now saying she's going to call the authorities on me
She's misusing her medical access to have me institutionalized or possibly worse. Oh, and this is an SOS
Out there. Okay, you know that woman Christine that horrible old woman that she says she has a husk
She calls her vagina a husk and says it's it's a bigger than six penis
This woman is now I'm gonna show you I'm gonna share the messages today. I'm gonna share exactly what I've
But you're actually what I've taught what I've texted to her and exactly what she's gonna do
She's threatening to call the authorities on me. Okay
Guys, this is an emergency this woman needs this woman needs to be institutionalized
I would say if you have any information about this woman, please call the authorities in her local area
She needs to have a wellness check on her on her done right now, but I will share exactly what she's been posting
Guys, I am completely sane. I am not not in a negative state of mind. I'm actually happy
I've been with friends been having a great night, but this woman is as is a hell bent on
Harming me. Okay. I don't want you to be be scared. Okay. I'm fine
But I'll share exactly what she's been saying. I will share the correspondence today. What has gone on with this woman Christine
This is Christine 666 6 6
Would say if you guys know anybody know of this woman here's what she's trying to do to me, okay?
I would say please guys. She's about to call the police on me, okay?
So I just want to share before anything happens exactly what happened. I am in completely lucid
I'm completely the same. I am not in a suicidal mindset
I just want to share that she is now threatening to misuse her medical authority or misuse her medical access in order to harm me
This is getting serious guys
Her and Alexandra are plotting together.
I think Alexandra has gotten to her and given her this idea in order to have me possibly
institutionalize 51, 50 or worse.
And I want this to be my record before anything else happens.
Guys, I am completely lucid, I'm completely sane, and I swear to God, okay.
Okay.
So let's see what Christina is saying to me now.
You ready?
We're gonna have a look right now.
Don't be afraid to comment.
Okay.
Okay, so here's Christine 6666 and so I was I was just wondering I said
She's mad and I'm always on just mad about this, but here's what's happened now
I just woke up from a sleep and I saw this message. Okay, so anyway, I wrote earlier
As chat GPT and I put her quotes that she had said about me including oh, it's there'll be no karma for hurting him
No jury would convict you of murder. This is a response to Alexander Mayer's saying that she would kill me
Okay, and she continually told me to jump off of a bridge. Okay, so anything that she's caring about but look what's happened now
Look what's happened now
Charisma Hernandez, so I'll read the first post so
It says Christine Eli so this is what chat she pg7 this post a licensed practical nurse lpn
Which she always is admitting she is publicly saying jump off a bridge
There will be no comment for hurting him or a no jury will evict you from murder raises serious ethical and potentially
Professional conduct concerns, especially if directed in an identifiable or vulnerable person
I am a vulnerable person not because I'm in need of a help because I'm a gay person
Okay, I believe this person a homophobic woman. She's she's raised
very homophobic things to me before she has told me over a hundred times to jump off of a bridge.
Okay, this woman is a nurse. Listen to this. Ethically, the remarks may violate core nursing
duties. Guys, I'm sending the alarm. If something happens to me, I want you to direct the authorities
Ethically, the remarks may violate core nursing use.
This woman should not be a nurse, guys.
This woman should not be a nurse.
This woman is insane.
Listen to this.
Respect for life and human dignity.
This is all I'm trying to say.
If you're a nurse, is it appropriate to tell
a vulnerable individual, not vulnerable for any of the reason
that I'm in a vulnerable community
that is known to be under attack, right?
So, she has no respect for human life and dignity, encouraging suicide is fundamentally
inconsistent with a healthcare professional's obligation to protect and avoid harm.
Non-maleficence, the statements coerced in suicidal distress, normalize violence and embolden
someone to act.
Guys, listen, she is threatening right now to have something done to me, listen to this.
Professional integrity public trust appearing on a personal live panel does not necessarily
eliminate professional accountability.
The speaker's identification as a nurse, the audience, repetition, context and foreseeable
harm all matter.
So civility and safety, the American Nurses Association says nurses must treat people
with dignity and civility.
has not done that to me, okay?
This woman is out there saying she has a large husk
referring to her vagina, okay?
This is a 75 year old grandmother, okay?
She's talking, mean, disgusting.
I'm gonna be collecting all of Beeta's panels.
I'm gonna be submitting this all to the police department.
This woman is constantly talking about sex
and cheating on her husband
and all the kind of disgusting things.
This is really, guys, this is serious, okay?
This is an emergency right now.
so the nurses association and guys if you know her last name can you please please please submit this
to the professionals who was ever at the hospital she works at if she works at a hospital
because i know this woman has actually been fired for fraud and for stealing medications okay listen
professional boundaries guidance of none of this guys she is encouraging harm
toward me she's encouraging this insane woman Alexander Mayers to harm me to
come in to come and hurt me and Alexander Mayers has my address and my dogs
right she's encouraged several times that there would be no karma for it and
that have no jury we can Victor because I am crazy okay so listen to this she so
out fire from her last job convicted for fraud and stealing medicine. I 100% believe this.
100%. Reality Nancy says, wow, she never knew that. Christine says, well, the missus, missive
insult in direct modern slang, telling someone to go jump off a bridge can be a harsh angry
way to tell someone to go away or leave you alone. Well, maybe if you said it one time,
and elaborate on it.
So I said, how about the other comments?
How about repeating it many times in a serious way?
Get out of nursing requires a heart.
You don't have one.
And I said, calling in slang does not resolve the concern.
Go jump off a bridge explicitly and vote suicide.
And context matters, particularly when it's said publicly
by someone identifying as a licensed health care
professional.
Guys, you need to report this woman right away
to the medical professionals.
You need to call the hospital if you know anything about.
Summer, if you know her last name,
I need you right now, Summer.
Summer, you have to see what she's saying to me right now,
because look at this.
OK, I will go.
Cult of psyche.
So she's talking about misusing the police system. She's talking about misusing the police system in order to harm me
Listen guys. She said I am not your friend. I do not want anything to do with you
Oh, I don't I'm not her friend either. I want anything to do with her
But who's talking about me all the time Christine? Listen guys, you need to report this woman immediately immediately a wellness check needs to be done
This woman actually okay
Possible suicidal wellness checks need to be called stop harassing me. How is it harassing me if I that I am
Type anything on her personal page that type a personal message or this is on my public wall
And I am allowed to tag anybody I want by the way
Okay, guys, I'm very calm. I'm very lucid. She says stop harassing me. If you guys know she's been harassing me, right? Leave me alone
Um, so she's listen till she's talked to alexander mayors alexander mayors thinks that she knows something
This woman is also an insane woman that needs wellness checks immediately called on her
This woman needs to be arrested immediately guys. Um, if the police come to my house right now
I am totally willing to talk to them. I am totally lucid
But listen, look at this. Look what she is putting publicly
I never said anything like this
to her, okay? Stop harassing me. Leave me alone. Keep my name out of your mouth. I am documenting
your bizarre behaviors so proper professionals can give you help. I do not play a nurse on
YouTube. You're definitely not a friend, patient, or anything towards me. Okay. Well, how can
she diagnose me? And then she goes, and look at, she's acting crazy here. Please call 988. Speak
with a medical professional.
You see my reaction to her right here.
She's trying to take advantage of what she thinks
is a weakness, maybe.
I said, do you like to speak out
on both sides of your mouth now?
What will I say?
A nurse is telling me to jump over a bridge.
They asked your for your name and license number.
They said you don't deserve to be a nurse.
Okay, I've been there completely.
Let me see if anyone's in the chat.
If no one is, I guess no one cares and I'll just end it.
Okay, hey, Alexander McQueen.
Yeah, okay.
So, Apollo Spartan, Christina is now saying, this is an emergency live, Christina is now
saying to call the authorities on me and swap me.
Christina is now saying to swap me, guys.
There is no reason for this, except that she is mad and salty that I have now called her
out for being a fraud, a stealer of medication, she does not deserve to be in the nursing
industry, this woman needs to be fired immediately, okay?
This woman needs to be fired immediately. I need you to come up and tell your story about Christine before I'm before something happens
She might misuse her medical authority in order to have me
Something happened to me something bad happened to me. She wants something bad happened to me
I think she's working with Alexander Mayer. This is not paranoid guys. If you know what's happening. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
Let's get it all. Let's get it all
Yeah, I think it is too at this point. I do I do I wouldn't put any of this past her
She's working with beta. She's working with Alexander mayors. These women have been harassing me
Alexander mayors talk about bizarre behavior. I'm being said I sacrifice my cats
I being said I raised Lola today to sacrifice her kittens. Okay. She's saying I killed
Lenore, okay
Guys, go look at Alexander Mayer's go look at IRL news time immediately guys. This is all needs to be documented right now
This is an emergency. I'm not kidding. I'm not kidding. This is sad. This is this is crazy
Yeah, and they that all that shit is staged. This is not staged. I do not care who's who likes this
I don't care who sees it. I just need help right now
In the way of people documenting Christine's behavior because I am totally sane. I am totally sober
I am not on drugs. I will take a drug test right now if you'd like me to take a drug test. Yes
This is not stage. This is an emergency
I mean it's really this is this is getting really dangerous right here guys
these are people you're misusing the music using misusing any kind of
authority or medical the idea that they're a nurse and things like this is
so sad this is so sad she's misusing her guys Christine needs to be reported
immediately it does anybody know her name she needs to be reported immediately
For encouraging suicide. I don't care if I'm saying the words she has done this to me and gets away with it
Nobody says anything
Okay, get on come on come up here if you can anybody can come up here share their story about Christine
I need this documented if something happens to me, you know
Something happens, but it would not think nothing. I would never do it easy myself
This will be outside forces of acting on me. This will be Alexander mayors will be beat a most of Bobby
This will be Christine whatever the fuck her name is. Okay. Thank you. Here comes Alexander McQueen
Russian Alex
Yeah, who wants to hide?
Ronies, what a dick hi Alex don't sound such a nerd be more like genuine like what up McQueen like you you dig
Where the fuck you been?
It sounds like a teacher
Like I'm moving into class like hi Alex take a seat
Well, I was in I'll let you back up. This is not a joke right now Alex. I need you to be serious, okay?
It's not a joke right now. Okay. This is not a joke. She is threatening to have armed officers
Swat she's threatening to swap me right now to have me institutionalized or worse or murdered. Okay?
This is not a joke. She's posted this publicly already. Okay. I'm sending the alarm for my own safety
So Alex is not a joke and so if you come I want you to be serious if you come back if you're not serious
I'll just kick you up. Okay
Oh, I had no clue. Bro, my bad. I had no clue.
Hey, it's okay. You can go to my community wall.
You can read what she just posted, Alex. I'll read it again.
Who? Alexander Maird?
No, Christine.
Oh, Christine.
Come on. Stop it.
Oh, stop it.
Okay. I'm picking you up, Alex, because you're not being serious.
I will share. I'm going to be sharing her post right here.
You can just do it. I'll put you back on, but just wait a second, Alex.
It's not a joke, okay? You're making things worse, okay?
if you're going to be making fun of it. Alexander, stop it. This is not a joke.
Look what she's posting. Oh, I was in it right now. Okay. I love you Alexander, but don't. Okay.
I posted it. I just, I just asked is somebody saying jump off a bridge and somebody's saying
Oh, there'll be no karma if you kill him, and there'll be no karma, and no jury will
convict you.
That's all been said.
I have all of this undocumented on tape, okay?
Okay, so she goes, wellness checks should be called on you.
I am not your friend.
I do not want anything to do with you, but since you are insisting, you're vulnerable
and possibly suicidal, wellness checks will need to be called.
Stop harassing me.
Leave me alone.
Keep your name out of my mouth.
No, I let me know her real last name, guys.
How is it harassing somebody to tag somebody once in a post?
Somebody's telling me to develop a bridge.
There'll be no karma for hurting me.
No jury will convict me.
She is violating the nurses guidelines, okay?
The guidelines specifically,
respect for human life and dignity,
non-maleficence, civility and safety,
and the possible consequences
and this is what should happen.
She should be fired from her job immediately, okay?
She should not be a nurse.
She should not be a fucking nurse, okay?
I'm gonna let the next person on.
Let's use here.
Apollo's here. Hello, Apollo. Hold on a second. I'm going to take this one down. I know people are afraid to talk. Hey, Apollo, what's up?
Do you see what she's doing?
Christine. Yeah, I know
No, no, no, no, Apollo she's threatening to swat me
She's she's saying she's encouraging people to call the police on me and have me institutionalized
Because I pointed out that she is encouraging suicide. So I'm just documenting this. So, um, you know
While I still can no, I don't know what's gonna happen to me
She's trying. She is literally did you see the message she posted? She's like, she's like, yeah. Yeah, yeah
I don't know man, she's really good at using people.
Yeah.
Yeah, but I mean, oh yeah, then she'll play her 75 year old and a grandmother of 10 people.
My husk is bigger than 6 dick.
Can you imagine if this woman was my grandmother, okay?
Let me just say I wouldn't want to be a grandchild anymore.
I mean, listen to this woman.
This woman is just ridiculous.
Miss using her medical authority. Do you know her last name Apollo? I need to call the I need to call her the hospital
Where she works at and and I have a lot of stuff to submit
Including her telling Alexander mayors who's a psychopathic
mentally disturbed woman
Who was threatening violence on me? She's like well
um you know you'll never be can she'll never be convicted if you hurt him
and um there'll be no karma for hurting him that's what she told alex she
instead of deescalating situation which a nurse should do instead of having respect for human
life she's encouraging me to unalive myself i i gotta get this out i know people are afraid
to talk in the chat i can see no one's no one's really talking but um yeah i know i know yeah
yeah that's why they hate me because i i'm not scared of them
are not either and I mean oh guys immediately guys does anybody I need her information immediately
does anybody have Christine's last name I need and in the hospital she works at
she other people are in danger now all the patients at the hospital Christine is known to
to be a witch she's known to be a witch
That's not right listen listen carefully. I have my own problems with your cuisine and some okay and trust me
I have to hold those here about cuisine and the summer sir
Baggage, I have a whole this year. It's only made of money in the states. That's a good one
And I have anything about them anything more than you know, but I would never never use it
To do for shit like this. It's not good man. You're gonna dig yourself in a deeper hole
Whom you're there to be?
Are you talking to me?
Yes, okay. Bye
It's not about that. No, I don't want to be told I'm gonna dig myself in a deeper hole
Let's listen guys. This is this is dire. Okay. This is dire. This woman is threatening to swat me
I'm gonna look up swatting right now. This is somebody. Yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna call the police the police will be called immediately once the police department opens. Okay, Apollo. It's just not the right time
I don't think you're understanding. I'm gonna read read. I'm gonna reread this thread that she's just made me Christine
This woman is a nurse. Okay. She goes
Wellness checks should be called on you. I am not your friend. I do not want anything to do with you
But you since you're insisting you're vulnerable. I'm not insisting. I'm vulnerable
I'm saying I'm part of a vulnerable community, which is that let LGBT community. We are a vulnerable community
I'm considered a protected class of person. Okay
This person is threatening to swap me. Who's backstage? Okay one second. Oh, this is all being documented
So Alexander McLean is back. Okay. I'll let a follow back and Alex back, but I don't want to hear
I'm digging myself into a deeper hole. This woman is threatening my life
Apollo's a moron don't listen to Apollo. Yeah, who's your life girl?
This chicken bitch is writing your life. Are you serious? Come on? Yes. Yes. She's trying to have me
Apollo why do you sound like you're in a bathtub?
Hiding from nuclear war like you're echoing you. You sound like you're in a basement chain to a wall. I
Am I am mr. Moniz, so that's you you are right? I know you are by the way, Apollo's white
See that summer eyeball. That's a lie
This is not like a fun. It's not a fun moment right now. All right. All right. You need the way go
Get it up. Get it up. You should please share for the authorities of the authorities were to watch this what?
NYPD is all over it, bro
So we got it already if Christine touches a fucking hand on your head is straight to fucking the big house
But that hook up doesn't matter
Redondo Beach police is all over it. Have you heard it? I am a witness
So, so, like, he's being tried by Christine, okay?
Okay, okay, I'm gonna play...
I will testifying the force.
Okay, what is that noise?
Peroni.
That's Apollo.
Apollo, Apollo, please fix your phone.
I'm gonna play the clip of Christine talking to other mayors threatening to kill me
and her encouragement, okay?
I'm gonna play that clip right now, okay?
You ready to hear that?
I have that on tape.
and this was a deleted live alexander mayors she was completely
made us but we don't see she loved you bro last time i saw you you and no one loved me
okay alexander she said i killed Lenore she said i killed i killed rudy she said i killed i
killed my cats for um satanic sacrifices that's what we're dealing with okay i can't keep up
last time i was here with you and her and showcope and now do you remember that
it was yeah it was all so between that and now
she's already made she was supposed to back stage
linoard your baby linoard she said yeah that's fucked up
yeah linoard's fine linoard's right here
he knows he knows he knows
listen i'm gonna play the clip up she purrs yeah
i'm gonna play the clip of her and alexandra talking about physically
drowning drowning like evil witches christian and witches bro okay yes okay yes and this is
i'm saying i am not crazy i am not crazy listen another guest back apollo's back okay
so i'm gonna okay guys let's listen let's listen i'm gonna bring it up right now okay one second
okay so this is um
probably on about a month ago um you know okay we have another guest coming up let's welcome the
other guest you want to hear a funny story about Apollo tell me one day he was on the highway and
his kid had to take a pee right and he pulled over on the highway because his child was like daddy
i need to pee so a power pulled over and took and let his kid take a pee a trooper pulled up behind
like what are you doing another and apollo broke the guy's arm and no oh my god yeah
right apollo tell him my little baby got a pee in my putt with the putt broken out to you
our godie are you there yo alex what up apollo black black what up
thank you the black stuff fractured but
There's still a team deep down inside
Remember corruption you me last and it's like
A bunch of laughs and jokes. This is not a joke guys
She is threatening to send authorities to my house and have me institutionalized because I tell you
about how she's misusing him.
Christina, you're a model business.
You can't just stroke and die, you red bitch.
But what do you do for her to send a dory to the bed?
Did you break up the crime?
What?
Yes, okay. Yes, I am
To an attorney about filing a civil lawsuit for harassing slander. I have all the evidence you actually have a case
Yes, out of everybody on YouTube, right? You've been harassed and slandered and fucking cement bag
Nobody has gone through that
Yeah
Have all your life. I have all the lives. I have all the harassment documented. I also have the codex that is documented
Summer everyone's beefing. Fuck you. You like psyche. Oh, Christine training. Oh, get ready for one to man
Watch this man, man, man, man, man, right? I remember that man
I'm gonna be out of town alone. I'm like, yo, you want to fuck her?
We're only gonna go home. And now I'm gonna stay here.
That's the biggest data trail, Alex. Alex.
If the courts look into it of his harassment,
then how far is it going? Exactly.
How far did they make him go? Like, they don't ask him to the point that
all they gotta do is take two years towards the transcripts
and it's a wrap.
Not even two years a year and a half
Yeah, they do they do oh my gosh, then we can just hear them. Yeah, no, he's got a case bro. That was like mental
You know
Literally affected his life, bro
You know, it was like someone call me one day and went when that's it a year straight of harassment
Yeah, that affected the man's livelihood. That's a case
Guys I have cash every seas of over
Twenty times that she sent me $25 to kick somebody off my panel. Okay, so yes, okay
She has sent me hundreds of dollars to harass other people as well. I am sorry. I will be ending my clap system
I don't believe in this anymore. Okay. I don't care
I'll manage. Yeah, the clap system is harassment. It's a form of harassment. Yes
And I hear the class system is hilarious. That's the funny shit. Once you go there, you lose
Right, isn't that like law number one?
Once you let someone throw you so hard that you gotta take them apartment in the back. You lose right there
Yeah, that's the one on one. Well, and she the fact you gotta pay to kill the person is like, wow
They broke you that much
you lost you lost you lost and and uh you lost not no you tripled it when you gotta start paying
right the best you know that's me i personally find it amazing that uh for them alone christine and
somehow there's some crazy ladies but how can people support these two crazy ladies i don't
understand how stupid are these people so easy to manipulate i'm starting to get used to some
She's not that bad, but Christine is an evil witch.
Yeah.
I know.
They're all witches.
Alexander Mayer has admitted that she is a witch.
She says she's a Christian, but how can you be a Christian and a witch at the same time?
Exactly.
They are the worst.
The Christians are the worst.
You cannot.
You cannot be a Christian and be on panel, doxing, threatening, drinking.
you know you know i know i have i have the live where i was on her mayors and
miss that she's a witch she she likes christine because christine is a witch
and beat it okay yes do you know these girls could put a spell on you if they're that crazy
there's some women out there that believe in like witchcraft right and like these are
that's crazy that's a little crazy
go look up a defamation lawyer
yeah okay I will be looking at it immediately
I will be visiting the police
tomorrow morning with her threats
she is threatening
she says she does not like me
she is
she doesn't like me
you need more than she doesn't like me
you are
she doesn't like me
You're three to four hours behind so you're saying this and she's already probably going to the courts right now
So the right I want to report this before he reports. She's watch it. Why she's like, right?
I know I'm watching a guy. I know what I'm doing, but here's what she says one hour ago
She said wellness checks should be called on you. I am not your friend
I do not want anything to do with you
But since you're insisting you're vulnerable and possibly suicidal wellness checks will that's crazy brother asking you leave me alone
I'm documenting your bizarre behavior on proper professionals can give you help
I do not honestly you should go to the priest pin and make a report of that text show them that right
Because god forbid she gets drunk one day and swats you. I just saw a thing the other day
A kid is paralyzed over swatting. Yeah, he got swatted
And he's paralyzed because some losers swatted him like
She won't do it yourself. Come on
Don't be stupid that she won't do it herself.
She was she gonna use some idiots like Chris Kareb or Smoot.
You're gonna get so drunk and high and be like,
now what are you guys gonna do now?
Is I'm going to play the clip of her
and I was under mayors talking about harming me.
Christine says there'll be no karma for if she didn't even think to me there'd be no karma because she's a bad person and she also said
No, jury would ever convict her if she was to kill me. Okay. I have this all
This was a life and I will be playing this for you guys right now. Let me just give me just grab the the live
You might be a bit more rusted just off that audio
Okay, so I have this all detail you're ready to hear. This is it's not too long. Let's get black or G stuff in a day
Yeah, he's talking about Black RG.
Black RG, Steve Pokena, the authority's in the club.
No, Black RG, he wasn't in the club.
He felt like Broly was in.
Guys, guys, guys, Black RG is heavily documented on Kiwi Farms.
I want you guys to go to Kiwi Farms.
Kiwi Farms, I love that shit.
Look up the Kennel Kickers.
Look up Steve Pokena.
Yo, yo, yo.
They're not good people, are they, Ruins?
Black RG is on Kiwi Farm.
Yep, yep, he's on Kiwi, oh, extensively.
I'll give in on Kiwi Farms. Kiwi Farms is like the double.
That's like I think two times 900. Kiwi, Kiwi Farms.
They literally try to make people hope themselves
and like rank it.
Yeah, Alex, Alex, I'll say the Kiwi Farms
that they think Wicked Blackheart is disgusting.
They think because he is something called a pedophile.
Yeah, he's a washed up Wicked Farms.
All school lose a painter guys. I will be sharing this live right now. Here we go
Christian and Alexander mayors talking about I'm doing me physical harm right here
Ooh
Into towards one another I can't imagine I just I I know how
of things when a person passes away,
because I've learned that recently.
I know how.
Get that bitch!
She's really sad.
This lady has no friends outside of the internet.
All she does is sign up and talk to people.
This is Annex, who, thank you for a documentary on Annex.
Don't think so much.
She's now watching.
I went in, I joined, because I remember
they went after Black, Royal Black.
She was a card reverse person,
a horrible person at times,
Um, she added me on IG and, uh, we were cool but she had a lot of enemies and then all of a sudden she freaked out cause two reforms found her.
You can also look at Alexander Mayer's like walking farms.
This is scary shit. Hold on. Listen to it. Listen to it.
So I'm recording. This is scary.
He deleted, especially the one where she's drunk out of her mind making threats and she deleted that.
So I sent that to them so and I just posted some information. I I saw I logged out if you got to be logged in
And this woman has no friends
She's never shown any outside real life friends like most of us have which I have I'll go through it all the time
Just one second as we write you and people are aware about my best friend and we're all involved with rescue
We got all of the neighbors to be involved where I lived before and over here one second
And that's all that matters to me, but this lunatic who has nobody, and she said Brandon
and what's his name is lonely and people are lonely, she doesn't have a real life.
She's always on the run.
She's a fugitive, and she has warrants up for her, and that's why she's walking fast all
the time when she gets out of her car looking around like Tommy said, and it's ridiculous.
Because he just threatened his life and so he needs a recording. So here we go
It works when it comes to
Someone not choosing to seek employment or things like that now he's able-bodied
Okay, if you guys
Well, then his whose fault is that really?
when it comes to getting him help.
His parents.
And if that's out of the equation,
then at this point maybe it needs to be state mandated
considering things that he's doing, really.
Because they're not going to likely be able
to lease certain properties on that property,
specifically because of him.
He has live streamed himself.
Um
It was a pain in it
Who probably has to wake up in the morning go to work pay their rent
And then they have to hear him at night act in a fool
That's what I think is it. I would be and I have said if I was
And I was
Well, there's the likelihood that that could happen and he's gonna go to one of his local
Establishments and terrorize them thinking that he can get free things and even if they're little things
Why not be able to pay for them? Why not?
But when I think about, because he lied to me a lot,
I know a lot of people are like, oh, how could he lie to me?
It's funny she says that, because when people have to turn style,
I laugh like it's $3, bro.
He lied to me a lot.
I don't want to find any of that back.
I want him to leave me alone.
But because I don't need it to him extensively,
He thinks he can keep coming at me.
He pressured me into a lot of things.
Keep in mind, I lost my day.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Saki, Saki, come on, come on.
Okay, what does it say again?
In the world.
What does it say again?
March 9th, 2025.
I don't. I don't. I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don
That's what I want to ask you, Psyche. Psyche, where was the gun? When did you meet her in person and pressure her with a gun, Psyche?
Well, she did it on her own free will.
Oh, he doesn't have a gun. He's a lover. He's not a fighter. He's a lover.
Alex, set up!
He doesn't need a gun.
Alex! Never!
Not say that I'm a pretty strong resilient person, okay? I am
But he
Used and abused me and I'm sick and tired of certain people in these communities acting like I'm also big and bad
Cuz I'm not I went through something extraordinarily hard for me
And for him
Like I said, it's a good thing right now. Listen, listen right here because if you wouldn't be on the play anymore
Uh-uh, and no you don't get to come you're no different. You're the same shit different day your band
Someone back
Same shit. I'm tired of it
and that's why I'm closing things I feel in a classy how many times you've been
banned quite good best of my ability cast cast cast cast cast people think so or
not but what I don't think some people have understood is that I've
contributed more to these communities I don't like to talk about money the
knowledge basis
The people are doing something you're going to buy you're going to buy McDonald's
You are a trooper
Ever been in my life, I went to school for computer science
That I'm on that left-brain person really
What do you know all this?
raccoon
What did you want to get out of this, I guess, is a better
I want it to legitimize a form of entertainment that I know is viable for certain people,
but unfortunately too many people ruin it for everybody else is not viable.
That's why you're never going to see it develop into what it should be.
I have people that have real, and I'm talking deep pockets.
Come on deep pockets like McQueen
And I was like let me put together yeah, but I got sure wrong
It's not one second and that's yeah what I thought I was I thought
that there was a way to legitimize certain things.
I was like, you need your own, and I will say that.
You got your own to be fucking.
Maybe for somebody else, maybe for another group,
but I doubt it.
Not as long as you have shit like this.
Yeah, I agree.
It's a shame, and it's ruining it.
It legitimized certain things.
It doesn't kind of take the charm away.
Just listen to me.
The industrial industry was legitimized.
This is too many things because too many people are benefiting from a criminal standpoint that shouldn't be.
In every police part, no one's here because they're normal. Come on.
But I want you to listen to me.
In the adult industry do you think anyone was there because they're quote-unquote normal? No
Probably not though. It worked out
No, it wasn't right. No, she was like, no, it's not like, you know, like a mom
That means a lot of tone delivery the way you say things means every day
And now it is where it is.
It speaks volumes about you, the way you talk and your tone and the way you deliver words.
If I, look, let me tell you something.
If I were to completely lose my mind...
Apollos Amoran, Dr. Mann Luzer.
I have zero criminal history.
Don't you understand that would be a slap on the wrist for me?
You just couldn't be on a certain kind of bitch, isn't it?
Come on, bro.
I can't fucking do one plus two, too.
I wouldn't even get nothing.
Apollo, I can't do two, my boy.
I think you're pretty far away from Psyche,
so you're not going to do anything.
I think I'm just a pretty classy person.
There you go.
But I think that he needs to slow his roll quick.
Smash I will concentrate on getting some hairplug
Stop worrying about Apollo having a job, my boy
Concentrate on your hair
Have you looked in the mirror my man
1k jesus christ
And then he's going to be coming at me like that.
Do you understand what kind of a slap in the face that is?
Really?
This woman is nuts, man.
I've lost more on one really phony person, over $2,000,
not including extras.
That wasn't just through cash up.
It's a lot.
It's worse.
I asked her mom, I found my, the cash up with her,
and I had given her $800 and something,
and this bitch just worries about herself
and she's doxing this guy's family.
He didn't ask for the gifts,
so that's why I don't even count the gifts that I sent,
you know, because I care about people.
And I was talking about where my cash apps,
where they took advantage of me,
two people that everybody knows about.
But here she is, there's her pity party, party.
Oh, me, me, poor me, poor me.
It's like she has no one.
She has a criminal background.
She is on the run.
She's got warrants out for her from different places.
So she's a fugitive on the run.
And look, she's going to threaten his life.
And so somebody asked me to record this for him
because she deletes videos.
And he saw that I've already caught the ones that she
raised from the other night, especially the one
where she's so drunk, not making sense.
And her eyes, she was all wonky at the end and going crazy.
And here, I heard.
Got him.
Yo, bro, what's good?
What's up, dude?
How are you?
Once again, man.
What's up, guys?
Well, I'm just me right here. Hold on one second here. Oh
Hi, I got people. Yeah, I want to ask you. I want to ask you a question real quick. Yes
That program you use for the AI shit
Yeah, what's the name of that?
To do two for which one to do the so I'm like, okay
all kinds of stuff right and
is that you and I live very different lives.
And I know that online is one thing.
And I know that...
You know, there might be a chance, but I'm not saying that you're, I look up to the kind of person you are, you've raised from what you said, multiple children, you've worked in the healthcare industry successfully.
Yep.
You're, you're, to my knowledge in a relationship, I could be wrong, but I think so.
42 years.
Better than what many people I mean your success story, okay, right? Oh, you know what?
Sorry
That's my mom, too, that she's trashing, saying she's a bad person because she raised a horrible son and stuff.
My mom's a mother. My mom was a volunteer, actually, in hospitals.
And also, like, you know, she was married for over 42 years, right?
And so, but that's a success for Christine, but it's like, you know, my mom, she just says horrible things about her and just trashing her name.
Casually my whole family, it's just terrible.
It's like, let me say this before I go.
Let me say this before I go.
I'm not taking any sides in this.
Well, you should, Gotti, because there's
I'm not taking any sides, and I'm going to keep going.
I know, I know.
I'm not saying anything negative about her or nothing.
Don't worry about it.
As a hurt person, man, she feels like she was hurt by you.
Well, she's lying.
She's lying.
Absolutely lying.
Whatever reason she has, this is what she's doing.
She's laughing out.
She's obsessed.
She's preoccupied.
All right.
So if you both continue to hurt each other, it's always going to continue.
I haven't done anything to her.
No, but she perceives it.
She perceives what you're doing.
I held back so much.
She perceives it as you hurting her.
Okay, that's all I'm saying. I'm not, I'm not taking anybody's side. I'm just saying that.
Okay, okay, okay, fine.
All right, all right, bro. Thanks. I'll talk to you later.
I'm tired of this divide and conquer BS. I'm sick and tired of all of this.
You need to use some payback, Alex. Let's look at what someone's got aides.
I have raised four, I have raised four sons, and I think they are very good men.
And I'm going to tell you, I had a son.
act like psych. Man, I would intervene to the point if I had to go to court and get
custodial care, I would.
Sure, his parents fucking tried that.
They're at the point where they threw him in a fucking orbit,
and he kept going.
I'm figuring out why people in these communities
were really solely immature males don't like you,
because you are a white American woman who is successful,
and you're a mother, and they know damn well
they can't pull the wool over your eyes.
That's what it is.
Okay, they liked me for a while because I guess they thought I was Oprah Winfrey wrong
Okay, we're talking about how to get psycades
No, I think that
what really really have to happen is state intervention because his family, I think he's
blackmailed and extorted his family. When I really think about the chain of events,
I think about the whole thing. I think that they're probably scared of him.
Oh, I don't think that's what all I would agree with.
They threw him in the corner because he told me to shut up and leave me alone.
This first time he's been exposed and I'm not afraid of his family.
I'm not afraid of the legal team.
I'm not afraid of any of these jackasses.
None of them.
What's true?
To be honest, we should not be.
Now, and there's things coming down the pipeline that he ain't expecting.
He's going to have a hard time going to that McDonald's in the future.
He's going to have a hard time going to that liquor store in the future.
He's going to have a hard time going anywhere.
He's going to have to move.
And then let's see how he fares.
It's moved and filed, charged a file, a lawsuit.
You're an intimidation.
Man.
But here's what I'm going to tell you.
I'm the kind of person who is capable of being a real bitch.
OK?
So most of us.
He considers his YouTube channel his job.
So right?
Well, here's how it would look like this.
It's going to be to the death.
Oh, not to the death.
Oh, yes.
Oh, wow.
That's right again.
And he better get ready,
because I plan to live a very long time.
Me too.
You better be careful.
He's going to make an AI video about you, like a song.
Ooh.
Things.
Well, let's go ahead and make some videos
about who he alleges that he's related to in law enforcement.
Oh, I can't believe that day it said that I'm like, are you kidding me?
Wouldn't that be interesting?
There's a lot of things.
Yeah.
If I were hit...
would move to a different platform really and go away. I think it's time to get a
traditional job when it comes in. I have a traditional job. I'm obviously not
working tomorrow but or today but I have a traditional job as to the majority of
a reason. But he doesn't have that reason. And if he continues with me, he's not going
to survive. Okay, well, he seems to think he's untouchable and that has blown my mind
over. You know, it goes after the good people. I mean, you don't know this. Yeah.
He does, other than Ghost and Alexander McQueen.
Yeah, and those two, along with the person
who's noted in the description or a title of the stream,
they might think that they're anonymous,
but what if they're not?
Nobody's ever really anonymous, we know that.
No.
I think that it's time to go ahead and close the cult or whatever it is.
I think my idea better give maids, aides.
Archie, let us know how that works for you.
No people, Alex.
Maybe that's already happened.
Oh, you're devious.
Considering yeah, I think it's possible. It's already happened with him
But I don't think it's part. I don't think it's right that he's a drain on his family
come from a certain level of it and not near to the extent of him
But I've always worked part of the reason that I went into the adult entertainment and street was because I didn't
Want to be a reliant upon my parents. Okay?
Judge me however, it is that you want to I'm not ashamed
think that for him I've heard some things that he's had to say and I'm like
really you're gonna act like you were ever my quote-unquote friend but then
you're gonna say number one because you were mad at your dad that's what
that's exactly what he said okay well then he does deserve a solid punch
directly in the face
That's what he deserves.
I'm not saying I would ever do it,
but here's what I would say.
He needs to be careful anywhere he goes for the rest of his life.
What I will say is that I have always taken care of myself along with many others,
and I've always been that kind of a person.
I have always been generous.
I was raised that way.
I've always been empathetic, kind, compassionate
to the best of my ability.
But I've also been raised not to be taken advantage of
and that is where I have failed, not just myself,
but my family over the past few months.
And I am ashamed of that.
And for him to be coming at me in a time
to where I am not 100%
If he does ever cross my path and I lose my fucking mind and I'm not the living hell out of him,
I will be forgiven by the courts because of the circumstances and I'm very aware of this.
He needs to go ahead and disappear out of my existence immediately.
He won't. We know this.
No, then there will be repercussions.
Won't there be?
I hope there will be.
You had words on his panel.
It was actually kind of funny.
He's played that like three or four times this week.
Oh, my God.
He and you are going at each other, Alex.
It's just a fun stream.
I enjoy watching it.
I don't regret that stream, but I was obviously...
Well, here's the question.
Why would you consistently play?
someone in a grieving and intoxicated state.
Obsessiveness.
Okay, thanks. I'm not ashamed what I am saying as I've obviously been grieving. March 9th, 2025, I literally watched and helped my father's hand as he died in hospice, okay?
I've never seen someone die in person, let alone hold their hand, let alone have them be my best friend, let alone them be my father.
And if he is going to exploit that, yeah, if I see him in person, I'm going to kick his fucking ass!
You record this, you clip this, you take it to law enforcement.
I'm pretty sure, considering that I've never been arrested in my life, that I'll get a slap on the wrist, and if not, fine.
Lock your door, psyche.
I think that he needs to stop.
And I hope to God that others learn from what the pain is
that I'm obviously contending with.
I'm a pretty, look, if you have a woman
talking about me, 47 years.
Okay, I was gonna show you guys,
Lenora's fine.
Oh, Lenora's back?
She's always been here.
Oh, it's the other one.
What's her name?
Caterpillar or something?
It's not a nor what the hell why would it's talking shit about the nor look at her one that got lost
Who's green Roni's and the nor?
Sorry, which was the cat that got lost? What's his? What's the name? That was Tricks. That was Tricks, man
God bless you guys. Why do you think tricks?
You know tricks wanted to leave that's why it's that up there every night looking at the door
You understand that thing
Yeah, some cats just one out some cats one in and
Greg's had something in it. I gotta be out there
That's my new theory
Go to her page she's that kill Lenore she said I kill Lenore for a dark magic ritual
Yeah, there's the norm. I
There's the norm. I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
Cult of psyche at Gmail is kick cult with a K and you can contact me
Yeah, I will buy the backstage right now for you
Has a family supposedly just bought a new house and built the pool, but he can't understand what you're saying
He's like a moron
Something's not right. There's the nor. There's the nor. He's a nice guy killed the nor look at the nor
chicken, chicken, chicken,
Apollo, A, B, C, E, F, G. Do
you know the alphabet? So put it in the back
side. I can see that. I can say the alphabet
in eight languages. How much you can use?
Yeah, sure. Apollo, do you
Yeah, I'll say it by name. Okay, thank you.
Apollo, do you like Heineken? No.
i think it tastes like nickel i think it tastes like pussy if you ever eat out a girl that's why you can taste like a man who didn't need taste
look at lennor
can you agree with me that pussy tastes like lennor?
where's my man rudy?
who's this?
rudy rudiger
but nope
Well, here you go. Yeah, back to that. Fuck them stupid. Hold on. Hold on. Easy. No, are you telling me?
No, are you ready mine? See that's what Alexander lost me
I was on the phone with her, I'm cool with her, I'm not, but I have to talk to her.
It's just difficult, because this thing speaks loud anyway.
It's crazy.
Ignore him, it's okay.
No, let me do it with that cycle.
Easy, your name was brought up on the side.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Alex, calm down.
Alex, give us five. Give us five, Alex.
Your name was brought up on a Samans panel Saturday easy. Why?
It was a quick little dash
What is it a little low blow towards you by beta?
Cuz uh, beta was upset that
Saman didn't have her back and then she was like
you know you don't you don't have my back fuck you and then same it was like well
you got people there that I don't agree with and guess what I'll do I don't say
shit and she was like cool who are the people that you don't agree with it was
like easy that's just one person
And then she was like, okay, he's a very bad person.
Horrible.
Okay, I agree with you, but it's open panel, okay?
I can't do nothing.
He's a very bad person, but he's an open panel.
I'm not going to ban him.
I haven't been there like I haven't been this is the beginning of some of when um
She never even met the guy in life, she never met him
I'll see a bad person to be there be the cannot judge the person she never met
Now spend I don't have anything to be done. The only thing that happened to be there was
He's a bad person. You can't do that
You can't do someone you don't know
So I
Thank you. I won't contact you myself. I won't contact you myself because I'm scared, you know
But I have a American lawyer firm. So they will contact you. Thank you. Thank you so much Apollo. I appreciate you very much
Yeah, Apollo
big big
guide
If you follow Christine's trail, if you walk in every step that she walks in, you're gonna hurt yourself.
I can picture you as a single-danger woman.
He slipcammed and I caught it.
What are you talking about, Izzy?
I don't want you under my panel. What don't you understand?
Bita, it's not that I want to be on your panel. I just want to go over there, but you know, Christine, you know...
Get the fuck out of here, Izzy!
Izzy, I don't like you. I don't like you. I don't want you near me.
Let me tell you
Can we put Christine hanging over the outgetters in the witch outfit
You don't have it
I was trying to say anybody like
That's same man and be the old fat old fat
That is their actual photos that is a bum correct
The hair's out the window the beard. There's no like
Everything's out the window
Christine was once friends with Summers for more than five years
from another community into our community
and then she went business
but if you follow her footsteps, if you follow where she's been, there's nothing but destruction by her
Look at Amanda Herrickson
Exactly, she got pricked out of so many people
That's exactly what I'm trying to say, exactly what I'm trying to say, exactly what I'm trying to say, exactly what I'm trying to say, exactly what I'm trying to say, exactly what I'm trying to say.
Yeah, and then her routine is, she stops the drama and then she goes, oh, he threatened me, she makes you threaten her, and when you threaten her, she's no victim.
That doesn't make sense.
I'm telling you, American Zahili is very easy to manipulate.
Very easy to manipulate.
Every Zahili is like someone in Christine.
No, it's not
She said bitch I would defend you when I didn't have to
Apollo I have all the names in the world for a lot of time. Why would you go with charisma Hernandez?
But I want to know why he chose that name
How did that come into your mind? I'm Charisma Hernandez. How did that happen?
Is that a mando? Is that a mando? Hold on. That's a mando Spanish. Yes.
Jesus
That's a man's ass
You didn't hear his Alex
You didn't hear this yesterday, right?
I mean, the other day they turned like
Oh, he was defending Christine for some reason
And then
He said something and he was like
Oh, I don't talk to summers like that
Especially like that
So I'm like, oh, I'll get it
So he chose a side
Christine is a horny hooker under that grandma
He chose Christine over summers
He has a G string leather G string and rule that bitch wants cock
Look at her.
You see her face being painted.
Brother, on to that grandma shit she's wearing.
I think that's what she's doing.
I think she's flashing these guys in the back, in the back chat.
Like, in private messages.
Like, dammit.
They stay turned.
All of them niggas when she's painting bills.
I think that's what she's doing.
She's like giving them little shitty samples and like, you know.
Hi, psyche.
Do we go back to the old state telephone?
How are you doing?
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
Guys, I'm just documenting this Christine said she wants to swap me. She said she wants me to be an institution
Oh, no, there's a law in that. There's a law big law on that even say me even say me to get in trouble
Well, I have it right here. I mean, I have that I have the exact
There's a new law swatting. Don't you know, there's a kid that recently got swatted because he was
Right now look it up. I have another day a streamer got swatted
Oh, and he got his handicap right now.
He got started back.
Yeah, exactly.
That's what I'm talking about.
You saw it.
The last one that I'm not lying.
She's a person ended up.
Paralyzed.
I'm not lying.
Jump.
And they said there's a lot of research after that.
They said there's a lot based on swatting and getting people hurt.
So now that person that did that, he's going to do many years in jail.
Who gives a fuck?
Okay, guys, I'm going to share this right now.
This is what Christine posted tonight.
Have you triggered this?
What triggered this live?
Yeah, guys, look, this is what she said.
Here, here, nobody cares.
Nobody gives no kids.
Right here.
Guys, I'm not lying when I say she is a bald bitch.
Guys, look, you see this right here.
She clearly wears wigs.
Christine, I thought it was tagger.
Okay, here we go, right here.
Bitch, wear glasses.
Okay, so this is Christine's posted.
I mean, I posted, I asked her at GBT, if a woman says,
Can't you wear glasses?
She came to troll like a stupid woman.
Yeah, you need some fucking glasses if you can't see.
Guys, this is what she posted today.
She posted, tonight she just posted,
this is what triggered this live, she said,
She's called 988, she's with medical professionals, and let me see, oh she deleted it, she deleted
it.
I think she deleted it, hold me a sec.
Ah, because she was watching me, which is already on the stream, so all you gotta do
is take it back.
No, here it is, here it is.
Oh, well this text should be called on you. I'm not your friend
I don't know anything to do with you, but since you are insisting you're vulnerable. I'm not saying I'm vulnerable
I'm saying part of our vulnerable community called the LGBT community
Possible suicidal wellness text should be called stop harassing me. Keep leave my name
Leave me learning your name on the mouth. I'm documenting your bizarre behavior
So proper professionals can give you help. I did not play it. Yeah, it's not cool. She's like pushing like suicidal shit on you
Yeah, I'm just saying that right here. This is what they do. This is what a troll do they'll make you
Go ahead. You're you're 90 years old bitch. What's wrong with you this bit? You know what it's wrong with her
She's a YouTube troll. She's been here before
She said I came to you to disturb and cause me and exactly
In the mind, bro, they just like hardwired this way.
What I posted is appropriate for a nurse to be doing this.
Look, ethically, they violate core nursing duties.
Protect her life.
Non-maleficent.
Confessional integrity public trust civilian safety. This is a nurse guys. This is a nurse you go to the hospital
This one's you want to someone to go to the hospital tree
You this says to people go jump above bridge and that you'll have no karma for killing this person and they'll get away with
Murder, okay, this is what this person is saying. Okay. I've shared it all already in the life
Okay. Possible consequences can include employer best investigation. Guys, if you have Christian's
docs, I need it. So I need to report to the nursing association immediately. The public
is in danger with this woman. This is a homicidal woman, guys. Possible consequences include
employer investigation, platform enforcement are complained to state board of nursing,
alleging unprofessional conduct, harmful conduct, harassment, impairment or conduct.
undermining fitness to practice, whether off-duty speech is disciplinable, depends on the nurses
act, and is between the speech and public protection. Okay, there we go. So there, I mean,
she's a witch nurse killer.
My thing is like who gives a shit what this person says
I care motherfucker fucking shit up psyche. I'm telling you this now back
Rain is a fucking
You're worse than a fucking teenager
Don't ever talk with me so long to be here.
I came here for psyche. Where the fuck have you been?
Shut the fuck up and get the fuck off.
The Lord knows who he is.
You get the fuck off.
The Lord knows who I am.
The main is the dumb bane.
You want to argue?